http://www.merck.com/policy/terms-of-use/home.html

Skip to content
Terms of Use
These terms were last revised on August 3, 2020.
This website is maintained by Merck Sharp & Dohme Corp., a subsidiary of Merck & Co., Inc., Kenilworth, New Jersey, U.S.A. (“Merck”) and is intended for use by residents of the U.S. and its territories who are 18 years of age or older.
By using this website, you agree to be bound by, and to comply with, the terms of use on this page (“Terms of Use”). Merck reserves the right to change the Terms of Use from time to time, as necessary, and will provide notice, on this page, of any such changes, including the date they became effective. You may access this page at any time through the Terms of Use link at the bottom of each page on this website.
Nothing on this website should be construed as the giving of advice or the making of a recommendation regarding any decision or action related to your health or the health of others.  If you are a patient, you should consult a doctor or other qualified health care professional regarding any questions you have about your health or before making any treatment decisions. If you are a doctor or other qualified health care professional, you should not allow the content of this website to substitute for your own medical judgment, which you should exercise in evaluating the information on this website.
While it has used reasonable efforts to ensure that the information on this website is accurate, complete, and current, Merck expressly disclaims any warranty or representation regarding the accuracy, completeness, or currency of such information. THE INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” WITHOUT A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.
On this website Merck may collect, through registration processes or other means, personal information about you. Please refer to Merck’s Global Internet Privacy Policy for details about how we protect your personal information as well as Merck’s Global Online Tracking Policy regarding the types of cookies and similar technologies that our websites, web applications and other online services use and how you can control cookies on your computer or mobile device. You are responsible for the accuracy of any personal information about you that you provide to Merck through this website.
Except for information covered by our privacy policy, any communication or materials you transmit to or through the website, including data, comments, questions, suggestions, ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, or the like, shall become the property of Merck. Merck shall be free to use, disclose, reproduce, or distribute any such communications or materials without limitation of any kind.
This website may contain information brought to you by third parties or through links to other Internet websites. Notice of information or links of this kind is provided throughout the website. Merck does not control nor assume any responsibility for the information provided by third parties or the content of other Internet websites to which we provide links.
This website may include “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the safe harbor provisions of the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Merck undertakes no obligation to publicly update any forward-looking statement, whether as a result of new information, future events, or otherwise. Additional factors that could cause results to differ materially from those described in the forward-looking statements can be found in Merck’s most recent Annual Report on Form 10-K and the company’s other filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) available at www.sec.gov.
You should assume that all trademarks, logos, designs, slogans, and trade dress appearing on this website, whether or not appearing in large print, italics, or with the trademark symbol, are owned by Merck or its affiliate companies, or are used under license. This website may also contain or reference patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes, or other proprietary rights of Merck and/or other parties. No license to, or right in, any such trademarks, patents, trade secrets, technologies, products, processes, and other proprietary rights of Merck and/or other parties is granted to, or conferred upon, you.
You may not distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, repost, or use the content of the website for public or commercial purposes, including the text, images, audio, or video, without the written permission of Merck. You should assume that everything you see or read on this website is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used, except as provided in the Terms of Use or in the text on the website, without the written permission of Merck. Merck neither warrants nor represents that your use of materials displayed on the website will not infringe rights of third parties not owned by, or affiliated with, Merck.
Pursuant to Section 230 of the federal Communications Decency Act, providers of interactive computer services shall not be treated as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider. Although Merck may from time to time monitor or review discussions, chats, postings, transmissions, bulletin boards, and the like on the website, if any, Merck is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the content of any such Web pages or utilities nor for any third party’s error, defamation, libel, slander, omission, falsehood, obscenity, pornography, profanity, danger, or inaccuracy contained in any information within such pages or utilities on the website. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law.
Merck reserves the right, if you violate the Terms of Use, to suspend or terminate any account you have created on this website.
Related links
Forward-looking statement
Read our forward-looking statement
Cookie policy
Read our cookie policy
Privacy
Our privacy program begins with trust
Forward-looking statement of Merck & Co., Inc., Kenilworth, N.J., USA
This news release of Merck & Co., Inc., Kenilworth, N.J., USA (the “company”) includes “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the safe harbor provisions of the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. These statements are based upon the current beliefs and expectations of the company’s management and are subject to significant risks and uncertainties. There can be no guarantees with respect to pipeline products that the products will receive the necessary regulatory approvals or that they will prove to be commercially successful. If underlying assumptions prove inaccurate or risks or uncertainties materialize, actual results may differ materially from those set forth in the forward-looking statements.
Risks and uncertainties include but are not limited to, general industry conditions and competition; general economic factors, including interest rate and currency exchange rate fluctuations; the impact of the recent global outbreak of novel coronavirus disease (COVID-19); the impact of pharmaceutical industry regulation and health care legislation in the United States and internationally; global trends toward health care cost containment; technological advances, new products and patents attained by competitors; challenges inherent in new product development, including obtaining regulatory approval; the company’s ability to accurately predict future market conditions; manufacturing difficulties or delays; financial instability of international economies and sovereign risk; dependence on the effectiveness of the company’s patents and other protections for innovative products; and the exposure to litigation, including patent litigation, and/or regulatory actions.
The company undertakes no obligation to publicly update any forward-looking statement, whether as a result of new information, future events or otherwise. Additional factors that could cause results to differ materially from those described in the forward-looking statements can be found in the company’s 2019 Annual Report on Form 10-K and the company’s other filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) available at the SEC’s Internet site (www.sec.gov).
No Duty to Update
The information contained in this website was current as of the date presented. The company assumes no duty to update the information to reflect subsequent developments. Consequently, the company will not update the information contained in the website and investors should not rely upon the information as current or accurate after the presentation date.
Decline
Accept
You are leaving Merck.com
Cancel
Continue
Welcome to Merck.com
By continuing, you will be directed to a site intended only for residents of the United States and Canada. We are called MSD everywhere, except in the United States and Canada where we are known as Merck & Co Inc, Kenilworth, NJ USA
Continue
